<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Riccardo Lorenzon&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>http://pizzaandcode.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Riccardo Lorenzon&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 19:06:43 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://pizzaandcode.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Using AWS Vpc to set up a Wordpress application</title>
      <link>http://pizzaandcode.com/posts/vpc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 18:25:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pizzaandcode.com/posts/vpc/</guid>
      <description>For several projects i&amp;rsquo;m currently working on, a AWS Solution Architect associate certification is required.
I don&amp;rsquo;t actually believe in certifications as a way to prove any kind of knowledge, i found them useful to have an overview of how a certain product or service work and which kind of problems it&amp;rsquo;s meant to solve.
Having worked with AWS for more than 5 years i can say that i got my hands dirty with most of the topics involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a Chat application using Flask and React</title>
      <link>http://pizzaandcode.com/posts/chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 17:24:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pizzaandcode.com/posts/chat/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since my last post on this blog. I travelled a lot in the begin of this year, and i consider myself like to have done it before the global spread of the Covid-19.
I&amp;rsquo;m now working from home everyday, this saves me some time on the commute, that i can spend on reading and learning some new stuff. In this context i decided to create a chat application using React and Flask, mostly to try out new features of React 16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Hugo</title>
      <link>http://pizzaandcode.com/posts/hello-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 21:11:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pizzaandcode.com/posts/hello-hugo/</guid>
      <description>My first post on this blog is dedicated to the blog itself, and more precisely to the technology that i used to get it up and running.
First, i worked with a few CMS tools in the past, mostly for friends that wanted a quick page on the internet for their wedding, birthdays, etc etc. I remember how easy it was to set up a Wordpress website and make it beautiful by buying a 15$ template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://pizzaandcode.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 19:06:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pizzaandcode.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a software engineer currently working at kpn in the beautiful Amsterdam.
I&amp;rsquo;m also Italian, and because of that i&amp;rsquo;m supposed to love Pizza :)
I decided to start this blog to share my knowledge and the little gotchas i find every now and then.
For more info check my profile.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>